{
	"description": "アーヴ語",
	"deck": [
	{ "question":"アーヴ(の)〜", "answers":["バール・〜"] }, 
	{ "question":"アーヴ貴族", "answers":["バール・スィーフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"アーヴ史", "answers":["バール・グレール"] }, 
	{ "question":"アーヴ帝国", "answers":["バール・フリューバル"] }, 
	{ "question":"アーヴによる人類帝国", "answers":["フリューバル・グレール・ゴル・バーリ"] }, 
	{ "question":"アーヴ猫", "answers":["デューク"] }, 
	{ "question":"アーヴの腕", "answers":["バール・セーダ"] }, 
	{ "question":"アーヴの誇り", "answers":["バール・レペーヌ"] }, 
	{ "question":"アーヴの微笑", "answers":["バール・エヴォス"] }, 
	{ "question":"アーヴの都", "answers":["バール・ロニート"] }, 
	{ "question":"アーヴの名誉", "answers":["バール・レペーヌ"] }, 
	{ "question":"アーヴの流儀", "answers":["バール・ゲルサス"] }, 
	{ "question":"アーヴの歴史", "answers":["バール・グレール"] }, 
	{ "question":"愛の都", "answers":["ビロート・ネグ"] }, 
	{ "question":"愛の息子", "answers":["フルーク・ネグ"] }, 
	{ "question":"愛の娘", "answers":["フリューム・ネグ"] }, 
	{ "question":"アファレーシュ伯国", "answers":["ドリュヒューニュ・アファーレク"] }, 
	{ "question":"アプティック星系", "answers":["キーヨース・アプティカル"] }, 
	{ "question":"アプティック伯国", "answers":["ドリュヒューニュ・アプティカル"] }, 
	{ "question":"アプティック防衛艦隊", "answers":["レクポリア・アプティカル"] }, 
	{ "question":"アプティック防衛艦隊旗艦", "answers":["グラーガ・レクポレール・アプティカル"] }, 
	{ "question":"アプティック門沖会戦", "answers":["ライシャカル・ウェク・ソーダル・アプティカル"] }, 
	{ "question":"アブリアルの華", "answers":["グナー・アブリアルサル"] }, 
	{ "question":"アブリアルの耳", "answers":["ヌイ・アブリアルサル"] }, 
	{ "question":"アブリアル伯国", "answers":["ドリュヒューニュ・アブリアルサル"] }, 
	{ "question":"アブリアル伯爵", "answers":["ドリュー・アブリアルサル"] }, 
	{ "question":"天翔る迷惑", "answers":["ロビアシュ・セスラ"] }, 
	{ "question":"天川銀河", "answers":["エルークファ"] }, 
	{ "question":"天川門群", "answers":["ソードラシュ・エルークファル"] }, 
	{ "question":"網", "answers":["エーフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"新たな戦場へ", "answers":["ユクラーベ・ディーナ"] }, 
	{ "question":"暗号鍵", "answers":["セージュ・キームナ"] }, 
	{ "question":"位階", "answers":["レーニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"怒り", "answers":["セーロス"] }, 
	{ "question":"異郷への帰還", "answers":["サイロス・ロスロータジュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"育児園", "answers":["ソムローニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"育児休暇", "answers":["カグゾフォス"] }, 
	{ "question":"衣裳係", "answers":["ダウシャセール"] }, 
	{ "question":"衣裳筐", "answers":["ラワーフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"異状なし", "answers":["ゴスノー"] }, 
	{ "question":"一等勲爵士", "answers":["ラローシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"一般電波紋鍵", "answers":["セージュ・デファト・ヘータ"] }, 
	{ "question":"遺伝子検査", "answers":["ヤナルムコス"] }, 
	{ "question":"遺伝子提供者", "answers":["ラルリーヌ"] }, 
	{ "question":"遺伝要素", "answers":["デルラーシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"移動状態", "answers":["ノークタフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"移動壇", "answers":["ヤーズリア"] }, 
	{ "question":"愛しき娘", "answers":["ファル・フリューム"] }, 
	{ "question":"イリーシュ王家", "answers":["ラルティエ・イリク"] }, 
	{ "question":"イリーシュ王国", "answers":["フェーク・イリク"] }, 
	{ "question":"イリーシュ門", "answers":["ソード・イリク"] }, 
	{ "question":"医療支援機", "answers":["クリュールポーク"] }, 
	{ "question":"初陣", "answers":["フィートラショス"] }, 
	{ "question":"ウィンブル門", "answers":["ソード・ウィンブル"] }, 
	{ "question":"ウェーレ公国", "answers":["レクリューニュ・ウェーレル"] }, 
	{ "question":"ウェスコー王家", "answers":["ラルティエ・ウェスコール"] }, 
	{ "question":"ウェスコー王国", "answers":["フェーク・ウェスコール"] }, 
	{ "question":"ウェスコー門", "answers":["ソード・ウェスコール"] }, 
	{ "question":"ウェムダイス子爵", "answers":["ベール・ウェムダイサル"] }, 
	{ "question":"ヴォービノート建艦厰", "answers":["ロール・ヴォービノータル"] }, 
	{ "question":"ヴォーラーシュ伯国", "answers":["ドリュヒューニュ・ヴォーラク"] }, 
	{ "question":"ヴォーラーシュ伯国管制", "answers":["ブリューセ・ドリューヒュン・ヴォーラク"] }, 
	{ "question":"ヴォーラーシュ伯爵家", "answers":["ドリュージェ・ヴォーラク"] }, 
	{ "question":"ヴォーラーシュ門", "answers":["ソード・ヴォーラク"] }, 
	{ "question":"ヴォベイルネー工厰", "answers":["ロール・ヴォベイルネール"] }, 
	{ "question":"ヴォベイルネー鎮守府", "answers":["シュテューム・ヴォベイルネール"] }, 
	{ "question":"ヴォベイルネー門", "answers":["ソード・ヴォベイルネール"] }, 
	{ "question":"宇宙", "answers":["ケサース"] }, 
	{ "question":"宇宙艦", "answers":["メーニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"宇宙空間", "answers":["ダーズ"] }, 
	{ "question":"宇宙港", "answers":["ビドート"] }, 
	{ "question":"宇宙の民", "answers":["ケサテュード"] }, 
	{ "question":"海亀の羹", "answers":["オートン・フィフェマル"] }, 
	{ "question":"麗しき頑固者", "answers":["クラソーノン・ノーワ"] }, 
	{ "question":"麗しき者", "answers":["ノーウォン"] }, 
	{ "question":"運搬船", "answers":["カソービア"] }, 
	{ "question":"衛生従士", "answers":["サーシュ・リアレル"] }, 
	{ "question":"液体石鹸", "answers":["サテュール"] }, 
	{ "question":"エストート公国", "answers":["レクリューニュ・エスタートル"] }, 
	{ "question":"謁見の広間", "answers":["ワベス・ベゾーロト"] }, 
	{ "question":"円匙", "answers":["クフォー"] }, 
	{ "question":"円扉", "answers":["ボード"] }, 
	{ "question":"王", "answers":["ラルス"] }, 
	{ "question":"王位", "answers":["ラルトラジュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"往還機", "answers":["フラーシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"往還艇", "answers":["フラーシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"王宮", "answers":["ラルベイ"] }, 
	{ "question":"王家", "answers":["ラルティエ"] }, 
	{ "question":"王国", "answers":["フェーク"] }, 
	{ "question":"王女", "answers":["ラルトネー"] }, 
	{ "question":"王女殿下", "answers":["フィア・ラルトネル"] }, 
	{ "question":"王殿下", "answers":["フィア・ラルト"] }, 
	{ "question":"幼子", "answers":["アソーグ"] }, 
	{ "question":"陥ちざるもの", "answers":["ダワトサリア"] }, 
	{ "question":"帯留", "answers":["アペズ"] }, 
	{ "question":"想い出", "answers":["ワベード"] }, 
	{ "question":"想人", "answers":["ヨーフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"折敷", "answers":["ドレース"] }, 
	{ "question":"愚か者", "answers":["オーニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"〜科", "answers":["ファズィア・〜"] }, 
	{ "question":"階級", "answers":["レーニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"会社", "answers":["ガリュール"] }, 
	{ "question":"花押", "answers":["グナファス"] }, 
	{ "question":"輝く者", "answers":["セーリア"] }, 
	{ "question":"鍵", "answers":["セージュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"鍵語", "answers":["セジョス"] }, 
	{ "question":"貨客船", "answers":["レビサーズ"] }, 
	{ "question":"隠し", "answers":["モスク"] }, 
	{ "question":"核融合弾", "answers":["スピュート"] }, 
	{ "question":"家政室", "answers":["バンゾール・ガリク"] }, 
	{ "question":"家政室主任家士", "answers":["アルム・ゴニュード"] }, 
	{ "question":"家宰", "answers":["ガポティア"] }, 
	{ "question":"火山", "answers":["キーガーフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"家臣", "answers":["ゴスク"] }, 
	{ "question":"家臣団", "answers":["ゴスクラシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"家臣どの", "answers":["ゴスク・ラン"] }, 
	{ "question":"加速", "answers":["カイムホス"] }, 
	{ "question":"家徴", "answers":["ワリート"] }, 
	{ "question":"閣下", "answers":["ローニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"家風", "answers":["ジェデール"] }, 
	{ "question":"ガムヴ公爵公子", "answers":["ヤルルーク・レークル・ガムブ"] }, 
	{ "question":"ガムテーシュ子爵領", "answers":["ベールスコル・ガムテク"] }, 
	{ "question":"家紋", "answers":["アージュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"硝子杯", "answers":["スィニューク"] }, 
	{ "question":"〜・環", "answers":["スペーシュ・〜"] }, 
	{ "question":"柑橘果汁", "answers":["テュール・ラシュバン"] }, 
	{ "question":"艦橋", "answers":["ガホール"] }, 
	{ "question":"慣習", "answers":["ダルファース"] }, 
	{ "question":"艦章旗", "answers":["グラー・モンガール"] }, 
	{ "question":"灌水浴", "answers":["グーザス"] }, 
	{ "question":"灌水浴室", "answers":["シル・グーザサル"] }, 
	{ "question":"管制", "answers":["ブリューセ"] }, 
	{ "question":"管制官", "answers":["ブルーセガ"] }, 
	{ "question":"管制機能", "answers":["ブリューセラジュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"管制室", "answers":["シル・ブリューセガル"] }, 
	{ "question":"管制室主任家士", "answers":["アルム・ブリューセガ"] }, 
	{ "question":"艦政本部長官", "answers":["セーフ・ヴォボト・メニョト"] }, 
	{ "question":"艦船", "answers":["メーニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"完全移動状態", "answers":["ノークタフ・バタ"] }, 
	{ "question":"乾燥機", "answers":["ビムーキア"] }, 
	{ "question":"艦隊", "answers":["ビュール"] }, 
	{ "question":"艦隊旗", "answers":["グラー・ビューラル"] }, 
	{ "question":"艦隊旗艦", "answers":["グラーガ・ビューラル"] }, 
	{ "question":"艦隊司令長官", "answers":["グラハレル・ビューラル"] }, 
	{ "question":"艦隊副官", "answers":["ルーキア・ビューラル"] }, 
	{ "question":"艦長", "answers":["サレール", "マノワス"] }, 
	{ "question":"艦長称号", "answers":["サレラジュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"監督", "answers":["ビュヌケール"] }, 
	{ "question":"記憶巣", "answers":["ボワゼプク"] }, 
	{ "question":"記憶片", "answers":["ジェーシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"機械教師", "answers":["オノワレイレ"] }, 
	{ "question":"機械清掃員", "answers":["クネク・コウィキア"] }, 
	{ "question":"旗艦", "answers":["グラーガ"] }, 
	{ "question":"機関", "answers":["セー"] }, 
	{ "question":"機関参謀", "answers":["カーサリア・セール"] }, 
	{ "question":"気閘室", "answers":["ヤドベール"] }, 
	{ "question":"気閘室艚口", "answers":["ロー・ヤドベル"] }, 
	{ "question":"技術元帥", "answers":["スペーヌ・ファゼール"] }, 
	{ "question":"技術者", "answers":["ファズィア"] }, 
	{ "question":"儀仗従士", "answers":["サーシュ・イダル"] }, 
	{ "question":"絆のかたち", "answers":["クレース・スィトン"] }, 
	{ "question":"貴族", "answers":["スィーフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"貴族社会", "answers":["スィームフェ"] }, 
	{ "question":"基地", "answers":["ロニード"] }, 
	{ "question":"軌道宮殿", "answers":["ベイ"] }, 
	{ "question":"機動時空爆雷", "answers":["サテュス・ゴール・ホーカ"] }, 
	{ "question":"機動酒保街", "answers":["ラクネーヴ・ホーカ"] }, 
	{ "question":"軌道城館", "answers":["ガリーシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"軌道塔", "answers":["アルネージュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"機動反物質燃料製造工場", "answers":["ヨーズ・ホーカ"] }, 
	{ "question":"機能水晶", "answers":["コス・キセーガル"] }, 
	{ "question":"気密膠剤", "answers":["ディーブ"] }, 
	{ "question":"義務", "answers":["スレムコス"] }, 
	{ "question":"客船", "answers":["レーヴ"] }, 
	{ "question":"給仕", "answers":["バーティア"] }, 
	{ "question":"宮中序列", "answers":["ダルムサス・ヴォフリール"] }, 
	{ "question":"宮廷", "answers":["フリリーシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"救命莢", "answers":["ウィコー"] }, 
	{ "question":"教官", "answers":["ベセーガ"] }, 
	{ "question":"凝集光", "answers":["クランラジュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"凝集光銃", "answers":["クラーニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"凝集光砲", "answers":["ヴォークラーニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"強襲輸送艦", "answers":["ルソーミア"] }, 
	{ "question":"嚮導突撃艦", "answers":["アルム・ゲール"] }, 
	{ "question":"協力要請", "answers":["ラドーフォス・ロフォト"] }, 
	{ "question":"玉座", "answers":["スケムソール"] }, 
	{ "question":"玉杯", "answers":["ラムテューシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"機雷", "answers":["ホクサス"] }, 
	{ "question":"機雷戦", "answers":["ホクサティオクス"] }, 
	{ "question":"機雷担当砲術士", "answers":["トラーキア・ホクササセル"] }, 
	{ "question":"緊急事態", "answers":["レスリアムロス"] }, 
	{ "question":"銀の枝と蝸牛", "answers":["ヤーズ・シュレンナ・ル・クラスビュール"] }, 
	{ "question":"空間機動要塞", "answers":["ロニーデ・ホーカ"] }, 
	{ "question":"空間放浪時代", "answers":["ゴー・ラムゴコト"] }, 
	{ "question":"空識覚", "answers":["フロクラジュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"空識覚器官", "answers":["フローシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"空間庭園", "answers":["デーヴ"] }, 
	{ "question":"空挺艦隊", "answers":["ビュール・ワケール"] }, 
	{ "question":"駆動炎", "answers":["アソート"] }, 
	{ "question":"組合", "answers":["ガリュール"] }, 
	{ "question":"クリューヴ王", "answers":["ラルス・クリュブ"] }, 
	{ "question":"クリューヴ王宮", "answers":["ラルベイ・クリュブ"] }, 
	{ "question":"クリューヴ王家", "answers":["ラルティエ・クリュブ"] }, 
	{ "question":"クリューヴ王殿下", "answers":["フィア・ラルト・クリュブ"] }, 
	{ "question":"クリューヴ門", "answers":["ソード・クリュブ"] }, 
	{ "question":"クローハ二二九門", "answers":["ソード・マトマトソクンナ・クローハル"] }, 
	{ "question":"軍衣", "answers":["セリーヌ"] }, 
	{ "question":"軍医", "answers":["ガイリート"] }, 
	{ "question":"軍医科", "answers":["ガイリート"] }, 
	{ "question":"訓育教官", "answers":["ベセーガ"] }, 
	{ "question":"軍役", "answers":["スリュームコス"] }, 
	{ "question":"軍楽従士", "answers":["サーシュ・アロヴォト"] }, 
	{ "question":"軍艦", "answers":["ウィクリュール"] }, 
	{ "question":"軍士", "answers":["ボスナル"] }, 
	{ "question":"軍事基地", "answers":["ロニード"] }, 
	{ "question":"軍匠科", "answers":["スケーフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"軍匠科翔士", "answers":["ロダイル・スケム"] }, 
	{ "question":"軍匠十翔長", "answers":["ローワス・スケム"] }, 
	{ "question":"軍匠列翼翔士", "answers":["フェクトダイ・スケム"] }, 
	{ "question":"燻腿", "answers":["リョポス"] }, 
	{ "question":"軍大学", "answers":["ヴォスクラ"] }, 
	{ "question":"軍令長官", "answers":["ワロズ・リュアゾン"] }, 
	{ "question":"軍令本部", "answers":["リュアゾーニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"軍令本部情報局", "answers":["リュアゾーニュ・スポーデ・リラグ"] }, 
	{ "question":"訓練生", "answers":["ケーニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"猊下", "answers":["ニソス", "ニソース"] }, 
	{ "question":"警衛従士", "answers":["サーシュ・レートフェク"] }, 
	{ "question":"ケイシュ一九三門", "answers":["ソード・キュトソクンビナ・ケイク"] }, 
	{ "question":"警鐘", "answers":["ドゥニート"] }, 
	{ "question":"軽輸送艦", "answers":["イサーズ・ソーラ"] }, 
	{ "question":"経理従士", "answers":["サーシュ・スケル"] }, 
	{ "question":"軽量艇", "answers":["メーニュ・ソーナ"] }, 
	{ "question":"激情の俘囚", "answers":["ロリューク・イサーロト"] }, 
	{ "question":"結晶陶質", "answers":["リュアボン"] }, 
	{ "question":"結晶網", "answers":["エーフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"結線", "answers":["キューム"] }, 
	{ "question":"決戦前夜", "answers":["ゴイライシャカル"] }, 
	{ "question":"ゲムファーズ伯爵", "answers":["ドリュー・ゲムファド"] }, 
	{ "question":"幻炎", "answers":["レニーヴ"] }, 
	{ "question":"幻炎艦隊", "answers":["ビュール・レニブ"] }, 
	{ "question":"幻炎艦隊司令長官", "answers":["グラハレル・ビューラル・レネブ"] }, 
	{ "question":"幻炎艦隊司令部", "answers":["グラーガーフ・ビューラル・レニブ"] }, 
	{ "question":"幻炎作戦", "answers":["クファゼート・レニブ"] }, 
	{ "question":"幻炎第一艦隊", "answers":["ビュール・カースナ・レニブ"] }, 
	{ "question":"幻炎第五艦隊", "answers":["ビュール・リューナ・レニブ"] }, 
	{ "question":"幻炎第三艦隊", "answers":["ビュール・ビーナ・レニブ"] }, 
	{ "question":"幻炎第一七艦隊", "answers":["ビュール・キュダナ・レニブ"] }, 
	{ "question":"幻炎第二艦隊", "answers":["ビュール・マータ・レニブ"] }, 
	{ "question":"幻炎第四艦隊", "answers":["ビュール・ゴーナ・レニブ"] }, 
	{ "question":"建艦厰", "answers":["ロール"] }, 
	{ "question":"建国帝", "answers":["スクルレトリア"] }, 
	{ "question":"元帥", "answers":["スペーヌ"] }, 
	{ "question":"幻想園の馬", "answers":["ワーフ・ギュームヒュン"] }, 
	{ "question":"鍵盤", "answers":["セゲース"] }, 
	{ "question":"検問ラ", "answers":["イショス"] }, 
	{ "question":"舷門歓迎式", "answers":["パトムサイホス"] }, 
	{ "question":"<ゴースロス>の戦い", "answers":["スラーショス・ゴースロト"] }, 
	{ "question":"珈琲", "answers":["スルグー"] }, 
	{ "question":"後衛翔士", "answers":["リニェール"] }, 
	{ "question":"紅玉", "answers":["ドゥー"] }, 
	{ "question":"後継者", "answers":["ゴルキア"] }, 
	{ "question":"光源弾倉", "answers":["ヤペール"] }, 
	{ "question":"公国", "answers":["レクリューニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"侯国", "answers":["レーバヒューニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"膠剤", "answers":["ディーブ"] }, 
	{ "question":"工作艦", "answers":["ダウスィア"] }, 
	{ "question":"高山", "answers":["ガーフ・ラーカ"] }, 
	{ "question":"公子", "answers":["ヤルルーク"] }, 
	{ "question":"光子科", "answers":["ファズィア・ダテュークリール"] }, 
	{ "question":"公爵", "answers":["レークル"] }, 
	{ "question":"侯爵", "answers":["レーブ"] }, 
	{ "question":"侯爵家", "answers":["レーブジェ"] }, 
	{ "question":"皇女", "answers":["ルエネー"] }, 
	{ "question":"公女", "answers":["ヤルリューム"] }, 
	{ "question":"工厰", "answers":["ロール"] }, 
	{ "question":"工場", "answers":["ヨーズ"] }, 
	{ "question":"公女閣下", "answers":["ローニュ・ヤルリューマル"] }, 
	{ "question":"皇女殿下", "answers":["フィア・ルエネル"] }, 
	{ "question":"合成樹脂", "answers":["ゲーニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"皇族", "answers":["ファサンゼール"] }, 
	{ "question":"皇孫女", "answers":["ルエボグネー"] }, 
	{ "question":"皇孫女殿下", "answers":["フィア・ルエボグネル"] }, 
	{ "question":"皇太子", "answers":["キルーギア"] }, 
	{ "question":"皇太女", "answers":["キルーギア"] }, 
	{ "question":"紅茶", "answers":["ソイ・アーサ"] }, 
	{ "question":"交通艇", "answers":["ポーニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"皇帝", "answers":["スピュネージュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"皇帝杖", "answers":["ルエグリュー"] }, 
	{ "question":"皇帝陛下", "answers":["スピュネージュ・エルミタ"] }, 
	{ "question":"号笛", "answers":["メー"] }, 
	{ "question":"高等法院", "answers":["スカス・ラザソト"] }, 
	{ "question":"降伏の儀式", "answers":["ドニー・レヒアコト"] }, 
	{ "question":"航法参謀", "answers":["カーサリア・リルビコト"] }, 
	{ "question":"航法士", "answers":["リルビガ"] }, 
	{ "question":"航法野", "answers":["リルビドー"] }, 
	{ "question":"閘門", "answers":["ソヒュース"] }, 
	{ "question":"航路", "answers":["ビール"] }, 
	{ "question":"護衛艦", "answers":["レート"] }, 
	{ "question":"護衛戦隊", "answers":["ソーヴ・メスゲール"] }, 
	{ "question":"護衛隊", "answers":["スューフ・メスゲール"] }, 
	{ "question":"ゴガーフ伯国", "answers":["ドリュヒューニュ・ゴガム"] }, 
	{ "question":"故郷", "answers":["ムロート"] }, 
	{ "question":"国章", "answers":["ニグラー"] }, 
	{ "question":"国民", "answers":["レーフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"ゴクローシュ建艦厰", "answers":["ロール・ゴクロク"] }, 
	{ "question":"腰帯", "answers":["ウェーヴ"] }, 
	{ "question":"ご主君", "answers":["ファル・ローニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"個隊", "answers":["スューフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"琥珀", "answers":["フティエーニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"子羊", "answers":["サゲーシュ・ソクリュズ"] }, 
	{ "question":"殺す", "answers":["アゲーム"] }, 
	{ "question":"根源貴族", "answers":["クロフェーク"] }, 
	{ "question":"金剛石", "answers":["ラテクリル"] }, 
	{ "question":"金色烏", "answers":["ガサルス"] }, 
	{ "question":"混沌の都", "answers":["ビロート・クネーグナ"] }, 
	{ "question":"宰相閣下", "answers":["ローニュ・ボーシム"] }, 
	{ "question":"宰相府", "answers":["ボーシミアシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"作戦参謀", "answers":["カーサリア・ヨクスクロト"] }, 
	{ "question":"作戦室", "answers":["シル・ヨクスクロト"] }, 
	{ "question":"下げ飾り", "answers":["フラーフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"ささやかな戦い", "answers":["スラーショス・スワーファ"] }, 
	{ "question":"座席帯", "answers":["アピューフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"餐堂", "answers":["ビスィアフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"参謀", "answers":["カーサリア"] }, 
	{ "question":"参謀徽章", "answers":["クラペーフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"参謀長", "answers":["ワス・カーサレール"] }, 
	{ "question":"散乱面", "answers":["シュノベズィア"] }, 
	{ "question":"似我蜂", "answers":["ロイル"] }, 
	{ "question":"指揮官徽章", "answers":["プトラヘデソーフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"指揮杖", "answers":["グリュー"] }, 
	{ "question":"識別電波紋", "answers":["デファス"] }, 
	{ "question":"時空分離", "answers":["ゴール・リュトコス"] }, 
	{ "question":"時空泡", "answers":["フラサス"] }, 
	{ "question":"時空泡発生機関", "answers":["フラサティア"] }, 
	{ "question":"時空融合", "answers":["ゴール・プタロス"] }, 
	{ "question":"時空粒子", "answers":["スプーフラサス"] }, 
	{ "question":"思考結晶", "answers":["ダテューキル"] }, 
	{ "question":"思考結晶網", "answers":["エーフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"侍従", "answers":["ベイケブリア"] }, 
	{ "question":"侍従長", "answers":["ワス・ベイケブレール"] }, 
	{ "question":"子爵", "answers":["ベール"] }, 
	{ "question":"子爵家", "answers":["ベーリェ"] }, 
	{ "question":"子爵殿下", "answers":["フィア・ベル"] }, 
	{ "question":"子爵領", "answers":["ベールスコル"] }, 
	{ "question":"氏姓", "answers":["フィーズ"] }, 
	{ "question":"姿勢制御機関", "answers":["ロイラーガ"] }, 
	{ "question":"次席翔士", "answers":["ロヤルム・ロダイル"] }, 
	{ "question":"使節庁", "answers":["ゲーク・スコファリメール"] }, 
	{ "question":"自走鞄", "answers":["ダグボーシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"士族", "answers":["リューク"] }, 
	{ "question":"士族さま", "answers":["キューク・リューカル"] }, 
	{ "question":"士族身分", "answers":["リュークラジュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"司厨従士", "answers":["サーシュ・クネイル"] }, 
	{ "question":"〜室", "answers":["シル・〜"] }, 
	{ "question":"執務室", "answers":["ガホール"] }, 
	{ "question":"質量波", "answers":["セースラズ"] }, 
	{ "question":"自動機械", "answers":["オヌホーキア"] }, 
	{ "question":"爵位", "answers":["スネー"] }, 
	{ "question":"射撃", "answers":["ウールタフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"修技館", "answers":["ケンルー"] }, 
	{ "question":"修技生", "answers":["ベネー"] }, 
	{ "question":"集合信号", "answers":["アーガ・アスパロト"] }, 
	{ "question":"集合邸宅", "answers":["バーシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"従士", "answers":["サーシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"従士長", "answers":["ウェサーシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"十翔長", "answers":["ローワス"] }, 
	{ "question":"重力制御", "answers":["ワムロス"] }, 
	{ "question":"重力制御機関", "answers":["ワムリア"] }, 
	{ "question":"主機関", "answers":["オプセー"] }, 
	{ "question":"珠玉", "answers":["ラーフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"淑女", "answers":["ロージュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"主計科", "answers":["サーゾイ", "サゾイル"] }, 
	{ "question":"主計後衛翔士", "answers":["リニェール・サゾイル"] }, 
	{ "question":"主計元帥", "answers":["スペーヌ・サゾイル"] }, 
	{ "question":"主計修技館", "answers":["ケンルー・サゾイル"] }, 
	{ "question":"主計修技館生活諸規則", "answers":["リウェール・クナソト・ケンルール・サゾイル"] }, 
	{ "question":"主計十翔長", "answers":["ローワス・サゾイル"] }, 
	{ "question":"主計准提督", "answers":["ロイフローデ・サゾイル"] }, 
	{ "question":"主計翔士", "answers":["ロダイル・サゾイル"] }, 
	{ "question":"主計前衛翔士", "answers":["レクレー・サゾイル"] }, 
	{ "question":"主計千翔長", "answers":["シュワス・サゾイル"] }, 
	{ "question":"主計大提督", "answers":["フォフローデ・サゾイル"] }, 
	{ "question":"主計提督", "answers":["フローデ・サゾイル"] }, 
	{ "question":"主 計百翔長", "answers":["ボモワス・サゾイル"] }, 
	{ "question":"主計副百翔長", "answers":["ロイボモワス・サゾイル"] }, 
	{ "question":"主計列翼翔士", "answers":["フェクトダイ・サゾイル"] }, 
	{ "question":"主思考結晶", "answers":["オブダテューキル"] }, 
	{ "question":"酒精", "answers":["スキアデ"] }, 
	{ "question":"主任(家士)", "answers":["アルム・〜"] }, 
	{ "question":"巡察艦", "answers":["レスィー"] }, 
	{ "question":"准提督", "answers":["ロイフローデ"] }, 
	{ "question":"准提督閣下", "answers":["ローニュ・ロイフローデル"] }, 
	{ "question":"乗員", "answers":["ソーク"] }, 
	{ "question":"商館", "answers":["ゲーク"] }, 
	{ "question":"城館", "answers":["ガリーシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"商館長", "answers":["ワス・ゲカル"] }, 
	{ "question":"称号", "answers":["トライガ"] }, 
	{ "question":"上皇", "answers":["ファニーガ"] }, 
	{ "question":"上皇会議", "answers":["ルゼー・ファニガラク"] }, 
	{ "question":"昇降台", "answers":["フェレトコーク"] }, 
	{ "question":"昇降筒", "answers":["ドブロリア"] }, 
	{ "question":"翔士", "answers":["ロダイル"] }, 
	{ "question":"翔士修技館", "answers":["ケンルー・ロイダル"] }, 
	{ "question":"翔士修技生", "answers":["ベネー・ロダイル"] }, 
	{ "question":"翔士適性審査", "answers":["ラデゥラジュ・ブークラグ"] }, 
	{ "question":"商船団", "answers":["カソベールラシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"商店館", "answers":["イレーヴ"] }, 
	{ "question":"少年", "answers":["ファネブ"] }, 
	{ "question":"掌兵科", "answers":["ボンデーブ"] }, 
	{ "question":"情報局", "answers":["スポーデ・リラグ"] }, 
	{ "question":"情報局長官", "answers":["セーフ・スポーデル・リラグ"] }, 
	{ "question":"情報連結", "answers":["ロンジョス・リラグ"] }, 
	{ "question":"照明", "answers":["アセルタフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"乗用艇", "answers":["ワーフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"勝利の舞い", "answers":["ワドロス・サーソト"] }, 
	{ "question":"勝利を", "answers":["サーソート"] }, 
	{ "question":"書記", "answers":["ウィグ"] }, 
	{ "question":"諸規則", "answers":["リウェール"] }, 
	{ "question":"飾帯", "answers":["クタレーヴ"] }, 
	{ "question":"諸侯", "answers":["ヴォーダ"] }, 
	{ "question":"諸侯家", "answers":["ヴォーダジェ"] }, 
	{ "question":"諸上皇の間", "answers":["ワベス・ファニガラク"] }, 
	{ "question":"所領", "answers":["スコール"] }, 
	{ "question":"司令", "answers":["サレール"] }, 
	{ "question":"司令官", "answers":["レシェーク"] }, 
	{ "question":"司令官室", "answers":["シル・レシェーカル"] }, 
	{ "question":"司令座", "answers":["グラハレリバーシュ", "レシェーキバーシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"司令座艦橋", "answers":["ガホール・グラール"] }, 
	{ "question":"司令長官", "answers":["グラハレル"] }, 
	{ "question":"司令長官殿下", "answers":["フィア・グラハレル"] }, 
	{ "question":"司令部", "answers":["グラーガーフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"司令部要員", "answers":["カボース"] }, 
	{ "question":"真空", "answers":["ダーズ"] }, 
	{ "question":"真空空間", "answers":["ダーズ"] }, 
	{ "question":"真空世界", "answers":["ダーズ"] }, 
	{ "question":"信号", "answers":["アーガ"] }, 
	{ "question":"人工子宮", "answers":["ヤーニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"寝室係", "answers":["ディアファセール"] }, 
	{ "question":"真珠", "answers":["ラーフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"ジントの怒り", "answers":["セーロス・ジンタル"] }, 
	{ "question":"真の翔士", "answers":["ロダイル・ノークタ"] }, 
	{ "question":"臣民", "answers":["ビサール"] }, 
	{ "question":"人類", "answers":["グレー"] }, 
	{ "question":"スィーヴ八八二門", "answers":["ソード・ガガマタ・スイブ"] }, 
	{ "question":"水耕農園", "answers":["グレーク"] }, 
	{ "question":"推進剤", "answers":["ビーズ"] }, 
	{ "question":"推進剤槽", "answers":["ビセーク"] }, 
	{ "question":"推進銃", "answers":["ワーリア"] }, 
	{ "question":"水素運搬船", "answers":["カソービア・ベンデル"] }, 
	{ "question":"スィトゥール捕虜収容所", "answers":["ロニューグヴィ・スィトゥル"] }, 
	{ "question":"スカレーシュ門沖会戦", "answers":["ライシャカル・ウェク・ソーダル・スカレク"] }, 
	{ "question":"スキール王家", "answers":["ラルティエ・スキル"] }, 
	{ "question":"砂芝", "answers":["ロンレーヴ"] }, 
	{ "question":"スファグノーフ基地", "answers":["ロニード・スファグノム"] }, 
	{ "question":"スファグノーフ侯国", "answers":["レーバヒューニュ・スファグノム"] }, 
	{ "question":"スファグノーフ侯国警固隊", "answers":["レートフェクラシュ・スファグノム"] }, 
	{ "question":"スファグノーフ侯爵", "answers":["レーブ・スファグノム"] }, 
	{ "question":"スファグノーフ侯爵閣下", "answers":["ローニュ・レーバル・スファグノム"] }, 
	{ "question":"スファグノーフ侯爵家", "answers":["レーブジェ・スファグノム"] }, 
	{ "question":"スファグノーフ子爵", "answers":["ベール・スファグノム"] }, 
	{ "question":"スファグノーフ子爵家", "answers":["ベーリェ・スファグノム"] }, 
	{ "question":"スファグノーフ子爵領", "answers":["ベールスコル・スファグノム"] }, 
	{ "question":"スファグノーフ伯国", "answers":["ドリュヒューニュ・スファグノム"] }, 
	{ "question":"スファグノーフ門", "answers":["ソード・スファグノム"] }, 
	{ "question":"スファグノーフ門沖会戦", "answers":["ライシャカル・ウェク・ソーダル・スファグノム"] }, 
	{ "question":"スポールの紅瞳", "answers":["キレーフ・ピアナ・スポル"] }, 
	{ "question":"スュール建艦厰", "answers":["ロール・スューラル"] }, 
	{ "question":"スュルグゼーデ王家", "answers":["ラルティエ・スュルグゼーデル"] }, 
	{ "question":"スュルグゼーデ王国", "answers":["フェーク・スュルグゼーデル"] }, 
	{ "question":"星界軍", "answers":["ラブール"] }, 
	{ "question":"星界軍軍士", "answers":["ボスナル・ラブーラル"] }, 
	{ "question":"星界軍元帥げんすい]", "answers":["スペーヌ・ラブーラル"] }, 
	{ "question":"星界軍翔士", "answers":["ラブール・ロダイル"] }, 
	{ "question":"星間船", "answers":["メーニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"制御篭手", "answers":["グーヘーク"] }, 
	{ "question":"制御卓", "answers":["クロウ"] }, 
	{ "question":"制御表層", "answers":["ファロール・ソク"] }, 
	{ "question":"星系内航行船", "answers":["ポーニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"成熟", "answers":["フェーロス"] }, 
	{ "question":"姓称号", "answers":["サペーヌ"] }, 
	{ "question":"成長", "answers":["ザーロス"] }, 
	{ "question":"青年", "answers":["ワンシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"星霧", "answers":["ヒール"] }, 
	{ "question":"セズレーニュ男爵", "answers":["リューフ・セズレン"] }, 
	{ "question":"接続纓", "answers":["キセーグ"] }, 
	{ "question":"前衛翔士", "answers":["レクレー"] }, 
	{ "question":"前皇帝", "answers":["スピュネージュ・レカ"] }, 
	{ "question":"戦士たち", "answers":["スラーケラク"] }, 
	{ "question":"千翔長", "answers":["シュワス"] }, 
	{ "question":"船艙", "answers":["ホール"] }, 
	{ "question":"戦隊", "answers":["ソーヴ"] }, 
	{ "question":"戦隊司令部", "answers":["グラーガーフ・ソブ"] }, 
	{ "question":"前男爵", "answers":["リューフ・レカ"] }, 
	{ "question":"前男爵閣下", "answers":["ローニュ・リュム・レカ"] }, 
	{ "question":"戦闘開始", "answers":["サポルガ"] }, 
	{ "question":"戦闘指揮卓", "answers":["ラトーニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"戦闘配食", "answers":["ワニール"] }, 
	{ "question":"先任〜", "answers":["アルム・〜"] }, 
	{ "question":"先任航法士", "answers":["アルム・リルビガ"] }, 
	{ "question":"先任参謀", "answers":["アルム・カーサリア"] }, 
	{ "question":"先任翔士", "answers":["アルム・ロダイル"] }, 
	{ "question":"先任通信士", "answers":["アルム・ドロキア"] }, 
	{ "question":"先任砲術士", "answers":["アルム・トラーキア"] }, 
	{ "question":"前バルケー王", "answers":["ラルス・レカ・バルケール"] }, 
	{ "question":"尖筆", "answers":["スュージュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"前フェブダーシュ男爵", "answers":["リューフ・レカ・フェブダク"] }, 
	{ "question":"戦列艦", "answers":["アレーク"] }, 
	{ "question":"造機科", "answers":["ファズィア・セール"] }, 
	{ "question":"艚口", "answers":["ロー"] }, 
	{ "question":"捜査", "answers":["ナテームコス"] }, 
	{ "question":"操作釦", "answers":["ポーシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"造船科", "answers":["ファズィア・ハル"] }, 
	{ "question":"造船技師", "answers":["ファズィア・ハル"] }, 
	{ "question":"造船修技館", "answers":["ケンルー・ファゼール・ハル"] }, 
	{ "question":"造船翔士", "answers":["ロダイル・ファゼール・ハル"] }, 
	{ "question":"装帯", "answers":["クタレーヴ"] }, 
	{ "question":"操舵士", "answers":["セーディア"] }, 
	{ "question":"操舵室", "answers":["シル・セデール"] }, 
	{ "question":"統帥府", "answers":["ワロディアシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"造兵科", "answers":["ファズィア・ロウボン"] }, 
	{ "question":"造兵修技館", "answers":["ケンルー・ファゼール・ロウボン"] }, 
	{ "question":"操泡担当航法士", "answers":["リルビガ・フラクトロショサセル"] }, 
	{ "question":"双翼頭環", "answers":["アルファ・マブラル"] }, 
	{ "question":"双翼の頭環", "answers":["アルファ・マブラル"] }, 
	{ "question":"隊", "answers":["スューフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"第一王女", "answers":["ラルトネー・カースナ"] }, 
	{ "question":"第一環", "answers":["スペーシュ・カースナ"] }, 
	{ "question":"第一艦隊", "answers":["ビュール・カースナ"] }, 
	{ "question":"第一艦隊司令長官", "answers":["グラハレル・ビューラル・カースナ"] }, 
	{ "question":"第一突撃隊", "answers":["スューフ・アシャル・カースナ"] }, 
	{ "question":"第一級臨戦態勢", "answers":["ヨグドズヴォス・カースナ"] }, 
	{ "question":"代官", "answers":["トセール"] }, 
	{ "question":"大公国", "answers":["ニーフューニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"大公爵", "answers":["ローニュ・ニム"] }, 
	{ "question":"大公爵家", "answers":["ニーミェ"] }, 
	{ "question":"大公爵公女", "answers":["ヤルリューム・ニム"] }, 
	{ "question":"第五艦隊", "answers":["ビュール・リューナ"] }, 
	{ "question":"第三艦隊", "answers":["ビュール・ビーナ"] }, 
	{ "question":"第十一環", "answers":["スペーシュ・ロキュトナ"] }, 
	{ "question":"第十一工場", "answers":["ヨーズ・ロキュトナ"] }, 
	{ "question":"第十二環", "answers":["スペーシュ・ロマータ"] }, 
	{ "question":"第一四艦隊", "answers":["ビュール・キュドゴナ"] }, 
	{ "question":"第一○五八突撃戦隊", "answers":["ソーヴ・アシャル・キュトポルリュガナ"] }, 
	{ "question":"大追跡", "answers":["ヴォーウェーコス"] }, 
	{ "question":"大提督", "answers":["フォフローデ"] }, 
	{ "question":"第七環", "answers":["スペーシュ・ダーナ"] }, 
	{ "question":"第二環", "answers":["スペーシュ・マータ"] }, 
	{ "question":"第二艦隊", "answers":["ビュール・マータ"] }, 
	{ "question":"第二級臨戦態勢", "answers":["ヨグドズヴォス・マータ"] }, 
	{ "question":"第二配膳室", "answers":["シル・スポーロト・マータ"] }, 
	{ "question":"大爆誕", "answers":["ドリアロン"] }, 
	{ "question":"第八環", "answers":["スペーシュ・ガーナ"] }, 
	{ "question":"第一二七船渠", "answers":["ルー・キュトマダナ"] }, 
	{ "question":"第一八四打撃戦隊", "answers":["ソーヴ・ヴォートゥト・キガゴナ"] }, 
	{ "question":"第四艦隊", "answers":["ビュール・ゴーナ"] }, 
	{ "question":"第四突撃隊", "answers":["スューフ・アシャル・ゴーナ"] }, 
	{ "question":"高坏", "answers":["スカリューシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"打撃戦隊", "answers":["ソーヴ・ヴォートゥト"] }, 
	{ "question":"打撃分艦隊", "answers":["ヤドビュール・ヴォートゥト"] }, 
	{ "question":"戦い", "answers":["スラーショス"] }, 
	{ "question":"旅立つ者たち", "answers":["レプラテラシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"ダルマプ門", "answers":["ソード・ダルマパル"] }, 
	{ "question":"探査艦隊", "answers":["ビュール・ラグレール"] }, 
	{ "question":"探査参謀", "answers":["カーサリア・ラグロト"] }, 
	{ "question":"探査担当通信士", "answers":["ドロキア・ロイロサセル"] }, 
	{ "question":"男爵", "answers":["リューフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"男爵閣下", "answers":["ローニュ・リュム"] }, 
	{ "question":"男爵館", "answers":["リューメクス"] }, 
	{ "question":"男爵家", "answers":["リュムジェ"] }, 
	{ "question":"男爵の家臣", "answers":["ゴスク・リュム"] }, 
	{ "question":"男爵領", "answers":["リュームスコル"] }, 
	{ "question":"誕生室", "answers":["ピュア"] }, 
	{ "question":"短針銃", "answers":["ケーリア"] }, 
	{ "question":"炭素結晶繊維", "answers":["リュルドワ"] }, 
	{ "question":"炭素結晶繊維紡錘", "answers":["ヨムセー・リュルドワル"] }, 
	{ "question":"短艇", "answers":["カリーク"] }, 
	{ "question":"端末", "answers":["ソテュア"] }, 
	{ "question":"端末腕環", "answers":["クリューノ"] }, 
	{ "question":"地上車", "answers":["フレリア"] }, 
	{ "question":"地上世界", "answers":["ナヘーヌ"] }, 
	{ "question":"地上世界出身者", "answers":["ナヘヌード"] }, 
	{ "question":"地上戦", "answers":["ナヘーヌヨクス"] }, 
	{ "question":"地上人", "answers":["アイブ"] }, 
	{ "question":"父の娘", "answers":["フリューム・ローラン"] }, 
	{ "question":"中心領域", "answers":["ソール・バンダク"] }, 
	{ "question":"〜長", "answers":["ワス・〜"] }, 
	{ "question":"長衣", "answers":["ダウシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"挑戦信号", "answers":["アーガ・イゾーフォト"] }, 
	{ "question":"勅任翔士", "answers":["セドラリア"] }, 
	{ "question":"直轄艦", "answers":["グラーバウリア"] }, 
	{ "question":"治療艦", "answers":["ジャースィア"] }, 
	{ "question":"鎮守府", "answers":["シュテューム"] }, 
	{ "question":"鎮守府司令長官", "answers":["グラハレル・シュテューマル"] }, 
	{ "question":"鎮守府副司令長官", "answers":["ロイグラハレル・シュテューマル"] }, 
	{ "question":"鎮守府副長官", "answers":["ロイグラハレル・シュテューマル"] }, 
	{ "question":"鎮守府本部", "answers":["バンゾール・シュテューマル"] }, 
	{ "question":"追撃戦", "answers":["ウェフソス"] }, 
	{ "question":"対消滅機関", "answers":["フリセースィア"] }, 
	{ "question":"通常宇宙", "answers":["ダーズ"] }, 
	{ "question":"通常空間戦", "answers":["ダディオクス"] }, 
	{ "question":"通信", "answers":["ドロシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"通信艦隊", "answers":["ビュール・ドロケール", "ビュール・ドロク"] }, 
	{ "question":"通信基地", "answers":["ロニード・ドロク"] }, 
	{ "question":"通信参謀", "answers":["カーサリア・ドロショト"] }, 
	{ "question":"通信士", "answers":["ドロキア"] }, 
	{ "question":"通話器", "answers":["ルオーデ"] }, 
	{ "question":"つなぎ", "answers":["ソルフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"椿の国", "answers":["スペシューニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝位", "answers":["スケムソラジュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝位継承", "answers":["キルグラジュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝宮", "answers":["ルエベイ"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝宮にて", "answers":["ルエベイル"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国", "answers":["フリューバル"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国艦隊", "answers":["ルエ・ビュール"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国艦隊司令長官", "answers":["グラハレル・ルエ・ビューラル"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国艦隊司令長官殿下", "answers":["フィア・グラハレル・ルエ・ビューラル"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国旗", "answers":["ルエ・ニグラー"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国貴顕録", "answers":["ルエ・ララサ"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国貴族", "answers":["ルエ・スィーフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国元帥", "answers":["ルエ・スペーヌ"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国公爵", "answers":["ルエ・レークル"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国侯爵", "answers":["ルエ・レーブ"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国高等法院", "answers":["スカス・ラザソト"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国国章", "answers":["ルエ・ニグラー"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国国民", "answers":["ルエ・レーフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国国歌", "answers":["ルエ・オル"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国宰相", "answers":["ルエ・ボーシフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国商船団", "answers":["ルエ・カソベールラシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国臣民", "answers":["ルエ・ビサール"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国星界軍", "answers":["ルエ・ラブール"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国星界軍管理区画", "answers":["ボレーヴ・ルエ・ラブーラル"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国創設以前", "answers":["バイ・ルエコト"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国代表", "answers":["ルエ・ルサーガ"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国男爵", "answers":["ルエ・リューフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国には勝利を", "answers":["サーソート・フリューバラリ・ア"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国の〜", "answers":["ルエ"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国の王女", "answers":["ラルトネー・フリューバラル"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国の国民", "answers":["ルエ・レーフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国の戦場", "answers":["ユクラーヴ・フリューバラル"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国の法", "answers":["ルエ・ラゼ−ム"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国の娘", "answers":["フリューム・フリューバラル"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国の揺籃", "answers":["ギュルソーグ・フリューバラル"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国伯爵", "answers":["ルエ・ドリュー"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国は汝を忘れじ", "answers":["フリューバル・ア・ダール・フローネデ"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国基準通貨", "answers":["スカール"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国副代表", "answers":["ルエ・ロイルサーガ"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国法", "answers":["ルエ・ラゼ−ム"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国紋章院", "answers":["ガール・スカス"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国紋章旗", "answers":["ルエ・ニグラー"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国暦", "answers":["ルエコス"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝国歴前", "answers":["バイ・ルエコト"] }, 
	{ "question":"梯索", "answers":["カリュグ"] }, 
	{ "question":"偵察戦隊", "answers":["ソーヴ・ウセム"] }, 
	{ "question":"偵察艇", "answers":["ボデーミア"] }, 
	{ "question":"偵察分艦隊", "answers":["ヤドビュール・ウセム"] }, 
	{ "question":"提子", "answers":["ロズギア"] }, 
	{ "question":"艇指揮", "answers":["ポノワス"] }, 
	{ "question":"停止状態", "answers":["スコールタフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝室", "answers":["ルエジェ"] }, 
	{ "question":"ティセーヌ伯国", "answers":["ドリュヒューニュ・ティセーナル"] }, 
	{ "question":"ティセーヌ伯爵", "answers":["ドリュー・ティセーナル"] }, 
	{ "question":"ティセーヌ伯爵閣下", "answers":["ローニュ・ドリュール・ティセーナル"] }, 
	{ "question":"停滞状態", "answers":["スコールタフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"艇長", "answers":["ポノワス"] }, 
	{ "question":"艇長徽章", "answers":["ブセスパス"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝都", "answers":["アローシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"提督", "answers":["フローデ"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝都交通庁", "answers":["スポーデ・ビル・アロク"] }, 
	{ "question":"帝都城館", "answers":["ガリーシュ・アロク"] }, 
	{ "question":"デメテル門", "answers":["ソード・デメテル"] }, 
	{ "question":"デルクトゥー宇宙港", "answers":["ビドート・デルクトゥール"] }, 
	{ "question":"殿下", "answers":["フィア"] }, 
	{ "question":"電磁投射砲", "answers":["イルギューフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"天節", "answers":["ディグル"] }, 
	{ "question":"電波通信", "answers":["ドロシュ・デム"] }, 
	{ "question":"電波虫", "answers":["デムブース"] }, 
	{ "question":"電波紋", "answers":["デファス"] }, 
	{ "question":"電波紋鍵", "answers":["セージュ・デファト"] }, 
	{ "question":"天浬", "answers":["ケドレル"] }, 
	{ "question":"ドゥガス猊下", "answers":["ニソス・ドゥガス"] }, 
	{ "question":"頭環", "answers":["アルファ"] }, 
	{ "question":"投降信号", "answers":["アーガ・レーガコト"] }, 
	{ "question":"ドゥサーニュ殿下", "answers":["フィア・ドゥサン"] }, 
	{ "question":"ドゥスーム猊下", "answers":["ニソス・ドゥスーマル"] }, 
	{ "question":"統帥府", "answers":["ワロディアシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"ドゥセーフ猊下", "answers":["ニソス・ドゥセム"] }, 
	{ "question":"逃走", "answers":["ディヘロス"] }, 
	{ "question":"ドゥネー星界軍大学", "answers":["ヴォスクラ・ドゥネール"] }, 
	{ "question":"ドゥヒール殿下", "answers":["フィア・ドゥヒル"] }, 
	{ "question":"ドゥビュース殿下", "answers":["フィア・ドゥビュト", "フィア・ドゥビューサル"] }, 
	{ "question":"同胞", "answers":["カルサール"] }, 
	{ "question":"透明面頬", "answers":["オベート"] }, 
	{ "question":"ドゥラーズ猊下", "answers":["ニソス・ドゥラド"] }, 
	{ "question":"独立戦隊", "answers":["ソーヴ・ゴラザサ"] }, 
	{ "question":"閉じた門", "answers":["ソード・レーザ"] }, 
	{ "question":"突撃艦", "answers":["ゲール"] }, 
	{ "question":"突撃艦長", "answers":["マノワス・ゲル"] }, 
	{ "question":"突撃戦隊", "answers":["ソーヴ・アシャル"] }, 
	{ "question":"突撃隊", "answers":["スューフ・アシャル"] }, 
	{ "question":"突撃隊司令", "answers":["サレール・スュム・アシャル"] }, 
	{ "question":"突撃分艦隊", "answers":["ヤドビュール・アシャル"] }, 
	{ "question":"弔いの晩餐", "answers":["ギューク・ロボロト"] }, 
	{ "question":"トライフ艦隊", "answers":["ビュール・トライム"] }, 
	{ "question":"トライフ艦隊旗艦", "answers":["グラーガ・ビューラル・トライム"] }, 
	{ "question":"歎く雉", "answers":["クテーシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"二等勲爵士", "answers":["キゼー"] }, 
	{ "question":"任務", "answers":["スコイコス"] }, 
	{ "question":"任務番号", "answers":["フタリア・スロフォト"] }, 
	{ "question":"猫目石", "answers":["デセーム"] }, 
	{ "question":"燃料", "answers":["ベーシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"燃料槽", "answers":["ベケーク"] }, 
	{ "question":"燃料槽小惑星", "answers":["ソブ・ベケーカル"] }, 
	{ "question":"ハイド伯国", "answers":["ドリュヒューニュ・ハイダル"] }, 
	{ "question":"ハイド伯爵", "answers":["ドリュー・ハイダル"] }, 
	{ "question":"ハイド伯爵閣下", "answers":["ローニュ・ドリュール・ハイダル"] }, 
	{ "question":"ハイド伯爵家", "answers":["ドリュージェ・ハイダル"] }, 
	{ "question":"ハイド伯爵公子", "answers":["ヤルルーク・ドリュール・ハイダル"] }, 
	{ "question":"ハイド伯爵公子閣下", "answers":["ローニュ・ヤルルーカル・ドリュール・ハイダル"] }, 
	{ "question":"ハイド伯爵城館", "answers":["ガリーシュ・ドリュール・ハイダル"] }, 
	{ "question":"培養牧場", "answers":["バセーヴ"] }, 
	{ "question":"ばか", "answers":["オーニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"鋼の心", "answers":["ソク・ジェンナ"] }, 
	{ "question":"伯国", "answers":["ドリュヒューニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"伯爵", "answers":["ドリュー"] }, 
	{ "question":"伯爵位", "answers":["ドリューラジュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"伯爵閣下", "answers":["ローニュ・ドリュール"] }, 
	{ "question":"伯爵家", "answers":["ドリュージェ"] }, 
	{ "question":"伯爵公子", "answers":["ヤルルーク・ドリュール"] }, 
	{ "question":"伯爵公子閣下", "answers":["ローニュ・ヤルルーカル・ドリュール"] }, 
	{ "question":"幕僚", "answers":["スペルーシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"箸", "answers":["グレー"] }, 
	{ "question":"馬上試合", "answers":["リエ・ドレール"] }, 
	{ "question":"旗", "answers":["グラー"] }, 
	{ "question":"八王国", "answers":["ガ・フェーク"] }, 
	{ "question":"八王家", "answers":["ガ・ラルティエ"] }, 
	{ "question":"八門の都", "answers":["ビロート・ガソーダル"] }, 
	{ "question":"八頸竜", "answers":["ガフトノーシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"抜錨", "answers":["ダイセーレ"] }, 
	{ "question":"母の息子", "answers":["フルーク・サーラン"] }, 
	{ "question":"同胞", "answers":["カルサール"] }, 
	{ "question":"薔薇の国", "answers":["パリューニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"パリューニュ子爵", "answers":["ベール・パリュン"] }, 
	{ "question":"パリューニュ子爵城館", "answers":["ガリューシュ・ベル・パリュン"] }, 
	{ "question":"パリューニュ子爵殿下", "answers":["フィア・ベル・パリュン"] }, 
	{ "question":"パリューニュ子爵領", "answers":["ベールスコル・パリュン"] }, 
	{ "question":"バルグゼーデ王家", "answers":["ラルティエ・バルグゼーデル"] }, 
	{ "question":"バルケー王", "answers":["ラルス・バルケール"] }, 
	{ "question":"バルケー王家", "answers":["ラルティエ・バルケール"] }, 
	{ "question":"バルケー王殿下", "answers":["フィア・ラルト・バルケール"] }, 
	{ "question":"番号", "answers":["フタリア"] }, 
	{ "question":"判定委員", "answers":["ラベスィア"] }, 
	{ "question":"反物質工場", "answers":["ヨーズ"] }, 
	{ "question":"反物質燃料", "answers":["ベーシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"反物質燃料工場", "answers":["ヨーズ"] }, 
	{ "question":"反物質燃料製造工場", "answers":["ヨーズ"] }, 
	{ "question":"反物質燃料槽検査船", "answers":["ラデウィア・ベケーカル"] }, 
	{ "question":"反物質燃料槽小惑星", "answers":["ソブ・ベケーカル"] }, 
	{ "question":"反陽子砲", "answers":["ルニュージュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"飛燕草", "answers":["リゼール"] }, 
	{ "question":"飛燕草の広間", "answers":["ワベス・リゼル"] }, 
	{ "question":"翡翠の玉座", "answers":["スケムソール・レン"] }, 
	{ "question":"ビスケース伯国", "answers":["ドリュヒューニュ・ビスケーサル"] }, 
	{ "question":"ビスレ伯国", "answers":["ドリュヒューニュ・ビスレル"] }, 
	{ "question":"飛翔科", "answers":["ガーリア", "ガレール"] }, 
	{ "question":"飛翔科翔士", "answers":["ロダイル・ガレール"] }, 
	{ "question":"姫さま", "answers":["キュアラ"] }, 
	{ "question":"百翔長", "answers":["ボモワス"] }, 
	{ "question":"標準重力", "answers":["デモン"] }, 
	{ "question":"開いた門", "answers":["ソード・グラーカ"] }, 
	{ "question":"広間", "answers":["ワベス"] }, 
	{ "question":"フェブダーシュ前男爵閣下", "answers":["ローニュ・リュム・レカ・フェブダク"] }, 
	{ "question":"ブェブダーシュ男爵", "answers":["リューフ・フェブダク"] }, 
	{ "question":"フェブダーシュ男爵館", "answers":["リューメクス・フェブダク"] }, 
	{ "question":"フェブダーシュ男爵館家政室", "answers":["バンゾール・ガリク・リューメクト・フェブダク"] }, 
	{ "question":"フェブダーシュ男爵家", "answers":["リュミェ・フェブダク"] }, 
	{ "question":"フェブダーシュ男爵帝都城館", "answers":["ガリーシュ・アロク・リュム・フェブダク"] }, 
	{ "question":"フェブダーシュの淑女", "answers":["ロージュ・フェブダク"] }, 
	{ "question":"フェブダーシュ門", "answers":["ソード・フェブダク"] }, 
	{ "question":"フェブダーシュ男爵領", "answers":["リュームスコル・フェブダク"] }, 
	{ "question":"フェブダーシュ男爵領管制", "answers":["ブリューセ・リュームスコル・フェブダク"] }, 
	{ "question":"フェブダーシュ男爵領暦", "answers":["フェブダーショス"] }, 
	{ "question":"父王殿下", "answers":["フィア・ローラン"] }, 
	{ "question":"副官", "answers":["ルーキア"] }, 
	{ "question":"副司令長官", "answers":["ロイグラハレル"] }, 
	{ "question":"副代表", "answers":["ロイルサーガ"] }, 
	{ "question":"副長", "answers":["ルーセ"] }, 
	{ "question":"副長官", "answers":["ロイグラハレル"] }, 
	{ "question":"副百翔長", "answers":["ロイボモワス"] }, 
	{ "question":"物質燃料・推進剤採取基地", "answers":["テューフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"埠頭", "answers":["ベス"] }, 
	{ "question":"舞踏の女神", "answers":["フトゥーネ"] }, 
	{ "question":"船乗り", "answers":["ソーク"] }, 
	{ "question":"船", "answers":["メーニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"浮揚車", "answers":["ウースィア"] }, 
	{ "question":"浮揚車発見", "answers":["ビリューコス・ウーセル"] }, 
	{ "question":"プラキア卿", "answers":["キュア・プラケール"] }, 
	{ "question":"プラキアの想い出", "answers":["ワベード・プラケール"] }, 
	{ "question":"プラズマ", "answers":["グノー"] }, 
	{ "question":"フリーザ伯国", "answers":["ドリュヒューニュ・フリーザル"] }, 
	{ "question":"分艦隊", "answers":["ヤドビュール"] }, 
	{ "question":"分艦隊司令官", "answers":["レシェーク・ヤドビューラル"] }, 
	{ "question":"分艦隊司令部", "answers":["グラーガーフ・ヤドビューラル "] }, 
	{ "question":"分艦隊紋章旗", "answers":["グラー・ヤドビューラル"] }, 
	{ "question":"ベートゥール建艦厰", "answers":["ロール・ベートゥル"] }, 
	{ "question":"兵員輸送", "answers":["レーヴァス"] }, 
	{ "question":"陛下", "answers":["エルミタ", "エルミトン"] }, 
	{ "question":"兵籍番号", "answers":["フタリア・ボスナル"] }, 
	{ "question":"平面宇宙", "answers":["ファーズ"] }, 
	{ "question":"平面宇宙技術", "answers":["ファズ・ファーゾト"] }, 
	{ "question":"平面宇宙航行技術", "answers":["ファズ・ファーゾト"] }, 
	{ "question":"平面宇宙航行機能", "answers":["メーンラジュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"平面宇宙航行", "answers":["ファーゾス"] }, 
	{ "question":"平面宇宙航行理論", "answers":["クロフェール・ファーゾト"] }, 
	{ "question":"平面宇宙航法", "answers":["ファーゾス"] }, 
	{ "question":"平面宇宙航法理論", "answers":["ソトフェール・ファーゾト"] }, 
	{ "question":"平面宇宙図", "answers":["ヤ・ファド"] }, 
	{ "question":"片翼頭環", "answers":["アルファ・クラブラル"] }, 
	{ "question":"法衣", "answers":["フェクセイ"] }, 
	{ "question":"防衛艦隊", "answers":["レクポリア"] }, 
	{ "question":"防衛艦隊司令部", "answers":["ガラーガーフ・レクポレール"] }, 
	{ "question":"防衛戦", "answers":["レクポロス"] }, 
	{ "question":"貿易港", "answers":["ビドート・アーサ"] }, 
	{ "question":"泡間通信", "answers":["ドロシュ・フラクテーダル"] }, 
	{ "question":"防御機雷戦", "answers":["ホクサティオクス・メジョト"] }, 
	{ "question":"防御磁場", "answers":["スネセーブ"] }, 
	{ "question":"防御磁場発生機関", "answers":["スネセーブガ"] }, 
	{ "question":"邦国", "answers":["アイス"] }, 
	{ "question":"紡錘", "answers":["ヨムセー"] }, 
	{ "question":"砲術参謀", "answers":["カーサリア・トラショト"] }, 
	{ "question":"砲術士", "answers":["トラーキア"] }, 
	{ "question":"放蕩娘", "answers":["ドルフリューム"] }, 
	{ "question":"補給艦", "answers":["ディーホスフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"補給参謀", "answers":["カーサリア・ソベール"] }, 
	{ "question":"補給戦隊", "answers":["ソーヴ・ディクポーレール"] }, 
	{ "question":"補給分艦隊", "answers":["ヤドビュール・ディクポーレール"] }, 
	{ "question":"星たち", "answers":["グリューラシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"星たちの眷族", "answers":["カルサール・グリューラク"] }, 
	{ "question":"募集事務所", "answers":["バンゾール・ルドロト"] }, 
	{ "question":"本部戦隊", "answers":["ソーヴ・グラール"] }, 
	{ "question":"麻酔銃", "answers":["リブアスィア"] }, 
	{ "question":"鱒の麭包み", "answers":["デルスルーフ・ボス"] }, 
	{ "question":"愛娘", "answers":["フリューム"] }, 
	{ "question":"ミスケル防衛艦隊", "answers":["レクポリア・ミスケラル"] }, 
	{ "question":"ミスケル門", "answers":["ソード・ミスケラル"] }, 
	{ "question":"未踏領域", "answers":["ソール・ケーラザ"] }, 
	{ "question":"都", "answers":["ビロート"] }, 
	{ "question":"無重力庭園", "answers":["ソムローニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"息子", "answers":["フルーク"] }, 
	{ "question":"娘", "answers":["フリューム"] }, 
	{ "question":"紫水晶", "answers":["ブレスキル"] }, 
	{ "question":"桃果汁", "answers":["ティル・ノム"] }, 
	{ "question":"門", "answers":["ソード"] }, 
	{ "question":"紋章", "answers":["アージュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"紋章院", "answers":["ガール・スカス"] }, 
	{ "question":"紋章旗", "answers":["ガール・グラー"] }, 
	{ "question":"薬剤科", "answers":["クリューリア"] }, 
	{ "question":"薬剤科翔士", "answers":["ロダイル・クリューレール"] }, 
	{ "question":"八つの頚をもつ竜", "answers":["ガフトノーシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"ユーニュ三〇三星系", "answers":["キーヨース・ビボルビナ・ユン"] }, 
	{ "question":"有翼竜", "answers":["ロース"] }, 
	{ "question":"輸送艦", "answers":["イサーズ"] }, 
	{ "question":"湯殿", "answers":["ゴーヴ"] }, 
	{ "question":"百合の国", "answers":["ギュリューニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"与圧兜", "answers":["サプート"] }, 
	{ "question":"与圧服", "answers":["ゴネー"] }, 
	{ "question":"溶岩松もどき", "answers":["ロドールムゼーシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"浴裙", "answers":["グーサス"] }, 
	{ "question":"浴室", "answers":["ゴーヴ"] }, 
	{ "question":"浴布", "answers":["ドゥヒュー"] }, 
	{ "question":"ヨニー伯国", "answers":["ドリュヒューニュ・ヨニール"] }, 
	{ "question":"予備役翔士", "answers":["ロダイル・キサイナ"] }, 
	{ "question":"四カ国連合", "answers":["ブルーヴォス・ゴス・スュン"] }, 
	{ "question":"四等従士", "answers":["サーシュ・ゴーナ"] }, 
	{ "question":"ラクテーシュ侯国", "answers":["ドリュヒューニュ・ラクリュク"] }, 
	{ "question":"ラスィース王家", "answers":["ラルティエ・ラスィーサル"] }, 
	{ "question":"ラスィース王国", "answers":["フェーク・ラスィーサル"] }, 
	{ "question":"ラフィール殿下", "answers":["フィア・ラフィル"] }, 
	{ "question":"ラフィールの変身", "answers":["ゴローコス・ラフィル"] }, 
	{ "question":"ラムリューヌ殿下", "answers":["フィア・ラムリューナル"] }, 
	{ "question":"ラムローニュ猊下", "answers":["ニソス・ラムロン"] }, 
	{ "question":"ラメーム猊下", "answers":["ニソス・ラメーマル"] }, 
	{ "question":"ラモーズ猊下", "answers":["ニソス・ラムロード"] }, 
	{ "question":"ラルブリューヴ鎮守府", "answers":["シュテューム・ラルブリュブ"] }, 
	{ "question":"リネー伯国", "answers":["ドリュヒューニュ・リネール"] }, 
	{ "question":"竜", "answers":["ノーシュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"竜の頸の付根", "answers":["サース・ノーシャル"] }, 
	{ "question":"領域", "answers":["ソール"] }, 
	{ "question":"領主", "answers":["ファピュート"] }, 
	{ "question":"領主代行", "answers":["クファリア"] }, 
	{ "question":"領主副代行", "answers":["ロイクファリア"] }, 
	{ "question":"領地", "answers":["リビューヌ"] }, 
	{ "question":"領民", "answers":["ソス"] }, 
	{ "question":"領民政府", "answers":["セメイ・ソス"] }, 
	{ "question":"領民代表", "answers":["セーフ・ソス"] }, 
	{ "question":"緑茶", "answers":["ソイ・アーラ"] }, 
	{ "question":"離着甲板", "answers":["ゴリアーヴ"] }, 
	{ "question":"林檎酒", "answers":["リンメー"] }, 
	{ "question":"ルーヌ・ビーガ市", "answers":["バーシュ・ルーナル・ビーガ"] }, 
	{ "question":"レスポー建艦厰", "answers":["ロール・レスポール"] }, 
	{ "question":"列翼翔士", "answers":["フェクトダイ"] }, 
	{ "question":"レトパーニュ大公国", "answers":["ニーフューニュ・レトパン"] }, 
	{ "question":"レトパーニュ大公爵", "answers":["ニーフ・レトパン"] }, 
	{ "question":"レトパーニュ大公爵家", "answers":["ニーミェ・レトパン"] }, 
	{ "question":"レトパーニュ大公爵公女", "answers":["ヤルリューム・ニム・レトパン"] }, 
	{ "question":"レトパーニュ大公爵城館", "answers":["ガリーシュ・ニム・レトパン"] }, 
	{ "question":"レトパーニュ門", "answers":["ソード・レトパン"] }, 
	{ "question":"檸檬", "answers":["ロープ"] }, 
	{ "question":"練習艦", "answers":["クレーヤガ"] }, 
	{ "question":"練習艦隊", "answers":["ビュール・クレーヤル"] }, 
	{ "question":"連絡艦", "answers":["ロンギア"] }, 
	{ "question":"連絡船", "answers":["パウリア"] }, 
	{ "question":"連絡艇", "answers":["ペリア"] }, 
	{ "question":"わが愛", "answers":["ファル・ネージュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"わが主", "answers":["ファル・ローニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"わが君", "answers":["ファル・ローニュ"] }, 
	{ "question":"わが主君", "answers":["ファル・スィーフ"] }, 
	{ "question":"わが娘", "answers":["ファル・フリューム"] }, 
	{ "question":"惑星改造技師組合", "answers":["ガリュール・ファゼール・ディウィム"] }, 
	{ "question":"惑乱の淑女", "answers":["ロージュ・ラビュルナ"] }, 
	{ "question":"忘れじの広間", "answers":["グレーシュ・フローネタラ"] }, 
	{ "question":"わたしの可愛い殿下", "answers":["ファル・フィア・クフェーナ"] }
	]
}